[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "apple",
        "back":"яблоко"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "orange",
        "back":"апельсин"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "cat",
        "back":"кот"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "dog",
        "back":"собака"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "living room",
        "back":"зал"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "bed",
        "back":"спальня"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "tomato",
        "back":"помидор"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "potato",
        "back":"картофель"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "carrot",
        "back":"морковь"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "ball",
        "back":"мяч"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "front": "doll",
        "back":"кукла"
    }
]